<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Life in IB</title><link>https://iblife.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Life in IB</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 21:18:27 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://iblife.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>IB students built a time machine to study 40 hours a day</title><link>https://iblife.github.io/posts/ib-students-time-travel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 21:18:27 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://iblife.github.io/posts/ib-students-time-travel/</guid><description>If you thought that the International Baccalaureate (IB) program was already hard enough, wait until you hear what some students have done to cope with the workload. A group of IB students from Singapore have reportedly built a time machine that allows them to study 40 hours a day.
The time machine, which resembles a large metal box with wires and buttons, was secretly constructed in the basement of the school library.</description></item><item><title>How a Biology HL Student Unleashed a Fungal Apocalypse After Getting 44/45</title><link>https://iblife.github.io/posts/biology-hl-fungi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 21:12:50 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://iblife.github.io/posts/biology-hl-fungi/</guid><description>You might think that getting a near-perfect score on your IB exam would be a cause for celebration, but for one unlucky student, it was the beginning of a nightmare. According to sources, the student (who wishes to remain anonymous) was so distraught by missing one point on his Biology HL paper that he decided to take revenge on his school by spreading a deadly fungus among his classmates and teachers.</description></item><item><title>IB Chemistry HL student arrested for possessing 1 tonnes of methamphetamine</title><link>https://iblife.github.io/posts/chem-hl-arrest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 20:46:24 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://iblife.github.io/posts/chem-hl-arrest/</guid><description>If you thought your IB Chemistry HL course was hard, wait until you hear about this student who took it to a whole new level. According to local news reports, a 17-year-old student from an international school in Singapore was arrested last week for possession of 1 tonnes of methamphetamine, also known as crystal meth.
The student, whose name has not been released for legal reasons, was allegedly involved in a large-scale drug trafficking operation that spanned across several countries in Southeast Asia.</description></item><item><title>IB Student tries to hang himself; fails because he didn't take Physics HL</title><link>https://iblife.github.io/posts/ib-suicide-fail/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 20:23:24 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://iblife.github.io/posts/ib-suicide-fail/</guid><description>If you are an IB student, you probably know the feeling of being overwhelmed by the workload, deadlines and exams. You might have even considered ending it all at some point. But before you do that, make sure you have taken Physics HL first.
That&amp;rsquo;s what one IB student learned the hard way when he tried to hang himself from a ceiling fan using his CAS hours log as a rope.</description></item><item><title>Rising fascism among IB Mathematics HL students</title><link>https://iblife.github.io/posts/math-hl-fascism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 20:13:54 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://iblife.github.io/posts/math-hl-fascism/</guid><description>If you are an IB student, you probably know what Mathematics HL (or Math Higher Level) is. It is a two-year course that covers topics such as calculus, linear algebra, probability, statistics and complex numbers. It is also one of the most challenging and demanding courses in the IB curriculum, requiring hours of homework, practice and revision.
But did you know that Math HL can also turn you into a fascist?</description></item><item><title>IB Students and Stimulant Use</title><link>https://iblife.github.io/posts/stims-ib/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 19:43:36 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://iblife.github.io/posts/stims-ib/</guid><description>If you are an IB student, chances are you have a secret stash of caffeine pills, energy drinks, or even stronger substances to help you survive the rigorous curriculum. A recent study by researchers at the University of Oxford has revealed that a staggering 99% of IB students are addicted to stimulants for staying awake.
The study surveyed over 10,000 IB students from around the world and asked them about their use of stimulants such as caffeine, nicotine, modafinil, Adderall, and Ritalin.</description></item></channel></rss>